flixxy.com 2019-03-21

# Flixxy.com Privacy Policy

**The privacy of our visitors to Flixxy.com is important to us.**

At Flixxy.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Flixxy.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on Flixxy.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick "DART" cookies**  
We also may use "DART" ( **D** ynamic **A** dvertising, **R** eporting and **T** argeting) cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [ //www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)  

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

(AdSense Privacy Policy provided by JenSense.com)   

Cookies may also collect non-personally identifiable information [what your search for] during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you.   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**  
How To Block Cookies**

To opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative's [opt out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).   
Additional information about deleting and controlling cookies can be found on [www.aboutcookies.org ](https://www.aboutcookies.org/)

**  
"No-Spam" Policy**

Flixxy.com maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. We are strongly opposed to unsolicited e-mail.  
Also, if you contact us by e-mail, your e-mail address will not be sold to a third party.  
If you subscribed to our newsletter, you can un-subscribe any time by clicking the un-subscribe link that appears at the bottom of each newsletter. 

Please [contact us](mailto:contactus@flixxy.com?subject=Comment%20about%20Flixxy.com%20Privacy%20Policy) if you have any questions and suggestions.

.
